<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Neo X Gene Movement on Larval Testis X Inactivation</title><link>https://jfear.github.io/larval_gonad_docs/docs/gene_movement/</link><description>Recent content in Neo X Gene Movement on Larval Testis X Inactivation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://jfear.github.io/larval_gonad_docs/docs/gene_movement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>D. Pseudoobscura (SP vs Cytes)</title><link>https://jfear.github.io/larval_gonad_docs/docs/gene_movement/dpse_gonia_vs_cytes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jfear.github.io/larval_gonad_docs/docs/gene_movement/dpse_gonia_vs_cytes/</guid><description>D. pseudoobscura (SP vs Cytes) I performed differential expression analysis by comparing cells in the SP cluster with cells in EPS, PS1, PS2, and PS3. I then took the list of genes from this analysis (SP-biased, Cyte-biased, Not Significant) and filtered out the orthologs. The majority of orthologs expressed in the germline were conserved with very few genes moving onto the respective Muller element (Table 1).
Table 1. Number of genes per Muller Element.</description></item><item><title>D. Pseudoobscura (SP vs EPS)</title><link>https://jfear.github.io/larval_gonad_docs/docs/gene_movement/dpse_gonia_vs_eps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jfear.github.io/larval_gonad_docs/docs/gene_movement/dpse_gonia_vs_eps/</guid><description>D. pseudoobscura (SP vs EPS) I performed differential expression analysis by comparing cells in the SP cluster with cells in EPS. I then took the list of genes from this analysis (SP-biased, EPS-biased, Not Significant) and filtered out the orthologs. The number of genes analyzed per Muller element and class are in Table 1.
Table 1. Number of genes per Muller Element.
muller_A muller_D muller_E conserved 46 100 141 moved_on 7 0 4 gene_death 34 23 20 moved_off 4 9 7 other 16 34 27 EPS Expression In Figures 1-3 I look at the proportion of EPS cells that expressed genes in the different movement classes.</description></item><item><title>D. Pseudoobscura (SP vs PS)</title><link>https://jfear.github.io/larval_gonad_docs/docs/gene_movement/dpse_gonia_vs_ps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jfear.github.io/larval_gonad_docs/docs/gene_movement/dpse_gonia_vs_ps/</guid><description>D. pseudoobscura (SP vs PS) I performed differential expression analysis by comparing cells in the SP cluster with cells in PS1, PS2, and PS3. I then took the list of genes from this analysis (SP-biased, PS-biased, Not Significant) and filtered out the orthologs. The number of genes analyzed per Muller element and class are in Table 1.
Table 1. Number of genes per Muller Element.
index muller_A muller_D muller_E conserved 80 151 218 moved_on 7 1 4 gene_death 31 21 27 moved_off 4 9 6 other 18 43 29 PS Expression In Figures 1-3 I look at the proportion of PS1, PS2, and P3 cells that expressed genes in the different movement classes.</description></item><item><title>D. Pseudoobscura (EPS vs PS)</title><link>https://jfear.github.io/larval_gonad_docs/docs/gene_movement/dpse_eps_vs_ps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jfear.github.io/larval_gonad_docs/docs/gene_movement/dpse_eps_vs_ps/</guid><description>D. pseudoobscura (EPS vs PS) I performed differential expression analysis by comparing cells in the EPS cluster with cells in PS1, PS2, and PS3. I then took the list of genes from this analysis (EPS-biased, PS-biased, Not Significant) and filtered out the orthologs. The number of genes analyzed per Muller element and class are in Table 1.
Table 1. Number of genes per Muller Element.
muller_A muller_D muller_E conserved 54 114 177 recent_conserved 0 0 0 moved_on 7 1 3 gene_death 34 20 24 moved_off 3 8 6 other 14 34 29 PS Expression In Figures 1-3 I look at the proportion of PS1, PS2, and P3 cells that expressed genes in the different movement classes.</description></item><item><title>D. willistoni (SP vs Cytes)</title><link>https://jfear.github.io/larval_gonad_docs/docs/gene_movement/dwil_gonia_vs_cytes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jfear.github.io/larval_gonad_docs/docs/gene_movement/dwil_gonia_vs_cytes/</guid><description>D. williostoni (SP vs Cytes) I performed differential expression analysis by comparing cells in the SP cluster with cells in EPS, PS1, PS2, and PS3. I then took the list of genes from this analysis (SP-biased, Cyte-biased, Not Significant) and filtered out the orthologs. The majority of orthologs expressed in the germline were conserved with very few genes moving onto the respective Muller element (Table 1).
Table 1. Number of genes per Muller Element.</description></item><item><title>D. willistoni (SP vs EPS)</title><link>https://jfear.github.io/larval_gonad_docs/docs/gene_movement/dwil_gonia_vs_eps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jfear.github.io/larval_gonad_docs/docs/gene_movement/dwil_gonia_vs_eps/</guid><description>D. williostoni (SP vs EPS) I performed differential expression analysis by comparing cells in the SP cluster with cells in EPS. I then took the list of genes from this analysis (SP-biased, EPS-biased, Not Significant) and filtered out the orthologs. The majority of orthologs expressed in the germline were conserved with very few genes moving onto the respective Muller element (Table 1).
Table 1. Number of genes per Muller Element.</description></item><item><title>D. willistoni (SP vs PS)</title><link>https://jfear.github.io/larval_gonad_docs/docs/gene_movement/dwil_gonia_vs_ps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jfear.github.io/larval_gonad_docs/docs/gene_movement/dwil_gonia_vs_ps/</guid><description>D. williostoni (SP vs PS) I performed differential expression analysis by comparing cells in the SP cluster with cells in PS1, PS2, PS3. I then took the list of genes from this analysis (SP-biased, PS-biased, Not Significant) and filtered out the orthologs. The majority of orthologs expressed in the germline were conserved with very few genes moving onto the respective Muller element (Table 1).
Table 1. Number of genes per Muller Element.</description></item><item><title>D. willistoni (EPS vs PS)</title><link>https://jfear.github.io/larval_gonad_docs/docs/gene_movement/dwil_eps_vs_ps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jfear.github.io/larval_gonad_docs/docs/gene_movement/dwil_eps_vs_ps/</guid><description>D. williostoni (EPS vs PS) I performed differential expression analysis by comparing cells in the EPS cluster with cells in PS1, PS2, and PS3. I then took the list of genes from this analysis (EPS-biased, PS-biased, Not Significant) and filtered out the orthologs. The majority of orthologs expressed in the germline were conserved with very few genes moving onto the respective Muller element (Table 1).
Table 1. Number of genes per Muller Element.</description></item></channel></rss>